http://www.sanctuaryseating.com/privacy-policy

Skip to content
This privacy policy sets out how bertolinidirect.com uses and protects any information that you give bertolinidirect.com when you use this website.
Bertolinidirect.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Bertolinidirect.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page occasionally to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 01/08/2020.
We may collect the following information from you:
Name and job title
Contact information including email address
Demographic information such as postcode, preferences, and interests
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather:
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with better service. We also require this information for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails, using the email address you provide, to inform you about new products, special offers, or other information which we think you may find interesting.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax, or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
CCPA
Bertolini respects your privacy. Your trust is important to us and we are committed to providing you with respect to the information we collect from or about you. Beginning January 1, 2020, the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (the “CCPA”) provides California residents with certain rights with respect to their personal information, including the right to opt out of certain disclosures of personal information.
Personal or organizational information collected by Bertolini often is limited to a phone number, mailing address, e-mail address, language, country or location, but may include other information when needed to provide a service or to reply with the information you have requested. We will not sell your information to any 3rd party businesses or advertisers.
We use the information we collect for customer support, marketing efforts, surveys, analytics and research, and other promotional activities.
To opt-out and/or delete the data that has been collected, please visit our Contact page and submit a request or email us at support@bertolinidirect.com.
Security:
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies:
A cookie is a small file to ask permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes, and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites:
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites. Other websites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information:
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
Whenever you are asked to fill out a form on the website, look for the option to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes.
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at bertolinidirect.com.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required to do so by law. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish for this to happen.
If you believe that any information we have on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Social distancing
products, solutions, and printable resources to help you worship safely.
X
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. For a complete overview of all cookies used, please read our updated Privacy Policy.Ok
